https://www.rivithead.com/articles/privacy.html

NEW PRODUCTSBootsCreepersHigh HeelsPlatform SandalsPlatform ShoesPlatform BootsShoesSneakersWomens CorsetsWomens ShirtsWomens PantsWomens SkirtsWomens DressesMens ShirtsMens KiltsMens PantsCoatsGlovesT-ShirtsBeltsChokersGauntletsWristbandsNecklacesEarringsBraceletsRingsWatchesMakeupGoggles and RespiratorsAccessoriesGifts and DecorCostumesCostume ShoesSteampunkCybergothCloseouts
0 items
Rivithead Privacy Policy
BY DAVID 02.18.14 09:51 PM
Tweet
Rivithead values our customers. Everything we do is focused on giving you a great shopping experience.
The information you share with Rivithead allows us to provide the service and products you have come to expect from us.
We believe in honesty and as part of providing an excellent shopping experience we strive to build a relationship of trust with our customers. Part of that trust relationship is to let you know in a clear and easy to understand way how we collect, use, share and protect your personal information.
Our Policy
What our privacy policy covers
How, why and what personal information we collect
How we Protect your personal information
With whom and what personal information we share
How you can limit the information we collect and share
Mailing list subscriptions
What does our privacy policy cover?
Rivithead's privacy policy covers how, why, use, protection and the sharing of your personal information on our website and will-call locations along with our business partners.
This policy focuses on information that can be reasonably linked to information that identifies you including your name, address, phone number, credit, debit, bank or PayPal information.
What type of personal information do we collect?
In plain terms we only collect information you share with us.
For example, you share information with us when:
You create an account on our website or mobile services
Participate in a contest, sweepstakes or promotion.
Request customer service or contact us
Make an in-store or online purchase with us
Post a review or comment on one of our social media pages, or post a rating, review or other content on our website.
We also collect:
Device Information: When you visit our site your browser identifies the browser version and information on if you are using a mobile device, desktop or tablet.
Referrers: The address of a referring websites.
Browsing information: We use web analitics, cookies and identifiers to collect information about the use of our website. These allow us to provide you with relevant information and products on our site. They also help us bring you the products you are most interested in.
Security surveillance: We deploy cameras in our warehouses and stores for security purposes only.
How we use your personal information.
We use your personal information to tailor your shopping experience. On product pages we may suggest other items you may be interested in or, in the rare occurrence, email you about a special or product you may be interested in.
Personal information is limited to employees that have a direct need to accesses it.
For example, our shipping staff does not need access to you browsing history, credit or other information not necessary to process and ship your order.
We also use your information for fraud prevention. We are very security aware and do everything we can to protect your information. Almost to a fault. We review almost 50% of the orders placed to make sure you were the one initiating the purchase. In the rare case we have to hold an order until we can contact you, please understand we are protecting your information.
Marketing: We occasionally send out coupons and information.
Advertising: We may use limited information such as email and tracking cookies to supply advertisements on products and promotions through third party advertising agencies.
How do we share your information?
We will not sell or rent your personal information. Period!
Under certain circumstances, such as fulfilling your order with a supplier, we may share limited information with trusted businesses or when legally required.
We share your browsing history with third parties such as google and Facebook. We never share your name, address, phone, credit or purchase history with any third parties that have no reasonable cause to collect such information.
How do we protect your personal information?
We will never sell or rent your personal information. We absolutely hate registering on a site only to get tons of spam and junk mail a day later.
We limit the information you supply to us with our employees at a need to know basis.
We will not disclose personal information over the phone or through email. We realize social hacking is a major problem in the world of today and will never disclose any personal information to anyone over the phone or through email.
We do not store credit card information.
Unlike many other retailers, we favor your security over convenience. Your credit card information, during checkout, is securly sent to the processor and then destroyed on our servers. We understand storing payment information makes it easier for you to checkout but, we see that as an unnecessary risk to your security with only a minor inconvenience to the checkout process.
Who do we share information with?
We limit the information we share with third parties and vendors.
In certain circumstances we may have to have your order shipped directly from one of our vendors. In this circumstance we share only the information needed to successfully deliver your order. (name, address, etc)
We share your browsing history with third parties such as google and Facebook. This includes pages visited, browser, device and IP address.
We never share your name, address, phone, credit, purchase amount, or purchase history with any third party such as Google and Facebook.
How you can limit the information we collect and share?
We may at times share information to third party agencies for the sole purpose of diplaying relevent ads and information to you. You may at any time opt out of our targeted ad campaigns by visiting Google's Ads Settings. Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Subscribe and unsubscribing from our mailing lists
You may opt out of our mailing by editing your account information and selecting unsubscribe to promo and sales emails in the account edit page.
Optionally you can unsubscribe from our mailings using the unsubscribe link found in all of our promotional emails.
If you did not create an account and are subscribed to our guest mailing list please click here. We will send you an opt out link to the provided address.
Rivithead may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please complete the contact form.
FOLLOW US ONFacebookTwitterPintrestBlogCUSTOMER SERVICEContact UsFAQ'sReturns & ExchangesOrder StatusCOVID-19 UpdatesSITE INFOPrivacy PolicyPrice GuaranteeSizing guidesShipping & Returns PolicyYour source for unique Gothic clothing and footwear since 1999.Copyright Rivithead ©2020 All Rights Reserved
